=A Love Journal=
= مجلة الحب =
=Episode 24=
= الحلقة 24 =
Sui.
سوي.
You are here.
أنت هنا.
I am.
انا.
Can you do me a favor?
هل يمكنك أن تسدي لي خدمة؟
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
Mr. Gu.
السيد.  قو.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Mrs. Gu.
السّيدة.  قو.
Hello, everyone.
أهلا بالجميع.
This is Gu Shen.
هذا هو قو شين.
Thank you all for your concern.
شكرا لكم جميعا على اهتمامكم.
But I want to tell you that
لكني أريد أن أخبرك بذلك
I am fine.
أنا بخير.
I'm here right now.
أنا هنا الآن.
Good idea.
فكره جيده.
Stand in the crowd
قف وسط الحشد
and the rumor ceases itself.
والشائعات تتوقف عن نفسها.
And,
و،
I would like to formally introduce my wife to you.
أود أن أقدم لكم زوجتي رسمياً.
Ning Sui.
نينغ سوي.
Great.
رائعة.
But...
ولكن...
He's...
إنه ...
He's gotten over it.
لقد تجاوزها.
How did he do that?
كيف فعل هذا؟
Ning Sui cured it.
عالجها نينغ سوي.
As long as Ning Sui is by his side,
طالما أن نينغ سوي إلى جانبه ،
he's fine.
انه على ما يرام.
I've known her for a long time,
لقد عرفتها منذ فترة طويلة ،
but I never thought she would have medicinal use.
لكنني لم أعتقد أبدًا أنها ستستخدم طبيًا.
Where did you go last night?
الى اين ذهبت الليلة الماضية؟
It happened so fast.
حدث ذلك بسرعة.
But,
ولكن،
we took this opportunity
انتهزنا هذه الفرصة
to eliminate some unnecessary troubles for the company
للقضاء على بعض المشاكل غير الضرورية للشركة
and clear some obstacles.
وإزالة بعض العقبات.
What about Mrs. Huang?
ماذا عن السيدة هوانغ؟
Mrs. Huang and Manager Sun got the information from somewhere
حصلت السيدة هوانغ والمدير صن على المعلومات من مكان ما
and spread it.
ونشرها.
But they've been convicted of libel
لكنهم أدينوا بالتشهير
by the relevant department.
من قبل الإدارة المختصة.
That's good.
هذا جيد.
I worried about you all night.
كنت قلقة عليك طوال الليل.
You worried about me all night?
أنت قلق علي طوال الليل؟
I...
أنا...
misspoke.
خطأ.
Zi Zhen.
زي زين.
Don't be angry with me, okay?
لا تغضب مني ، حسنًا؟
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
People are watching.
الناس يشاهدون.
So what?
وماذا في ذلك؟
I was kissing my girlfriend.
كنت أقبل صديقتي.
But...
ولكن...
What's going on with the suppliers?
ما الذي يحدث مع الموردين؟
We were not going to work with them.
لن نعمل معهم.
It's okay.
حسنا.
I have a diamond mine.
لدي منجم الماس.
Don't need to worry about the supply of raw materials.
لا داعي للقلق بشأن توريد المواد الخام.
I never thought
لم أظن طلاقا
I'd know such a rich man.
كنت أعرف مثل هذا الرجل الثري.
I'm not only a rich man,
أنا لست مجرد رجل ثري ،
but your man.
لكن رجلك.
(Ning Sui.)
(نينغ سوي.)
(Thank you.)
(شكرًا لك.)
(With you,)
(معك،)
(I dare to stand in the sun.)
(أجرؤ على الوقوف في الشمس).
(No.)
(رقم.)
(It is I who should thank you.)
(أنا من يجب أن أشكرك.)
(Because)
(لان)
(you're the apple of my eye.)
(كنت قرة عيني.)